If you think you know him, think again.
Meat Loaf: In Search of Paradise is a music,
documentary film directed by Bruce David Klein.
Meat Loaf, the legendary rocker, reveals surprising shades of himself -- and his
internal demons -- as he sets out on an ambitious world tour.
Self, played by Meat Loaf.
Self, played by Dennis Quaid.
Self, played by Kasim Sulton.
Self, played by Aspen Miller.
Self, played by Carolyn Coletti.
Self, played by Paul Crook.
Meat Loaf: In Search of Paradise is a 2007 independent documentary film that captures rocker
Meat Loaf and his life in rehearsals and on the road during his 2007 World Tour.
It was directed by Bruce David Klein and produced by Bruce David
Klein and Paulina Vera Williams by Atlas Media Corp.
in association with Voom HD Pictures and 10th Street Entertainment.
The film was an official selection of the Montreal World Film
Festival in 2007 and of the USA Film Festival in 2008.
In Europe, the film was included in the 3 Bats Live DVD.
According to Allmovie, "as the stage show gets more and more involved, the singer battles
ongoing health concerns."
The film was theatrically released in 75 cities in the U.S.
and Canada on March 12, 2008.
The premiere was held at New York City's IFC Center.
The New York Times called the film "amusing," and Variety said it was "revealing."  It is
now available on DVD from Universal and can be seen on television worldwide.